mydeco.com 2018-06-25

# MONOQI | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Dear visitors of our internet portal,  
In order for you to feel safe and comfortable when visiting our websites, we would like to inform you about the handling of your data below. 

1\. Responsible

Responsible for the collection, processing and use of personal data that is collected when visiting this website is the Things I like GmbH, Gormannstraße 22, 10119 Berlin (hereinafter also "MONOQI" or "we" called) 

2\. What these privacy policies govern

These data protection regulations regulate the handling of personal data. They describe which personal information we collect when using our website and how we use it. Personal data are individual details about personal or factual circumstances of a specific or identifiable natural person. This includes information such as your name, address, phone number or date of birth. Statistical information that can not be directly or indirectly associated with you - such as the popularity of individual websites of our website or the number of users of a website - are not personal data. 

3\. What data we collect and how we use it

1\. Usage Data

When you visit our websites, we temporarily store so-called usage data on the basis of Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. We use the usage data for statistical purposes in order to improve the quality of our websites and for security purposes. We also use this information to enable access to our website, to control and administer our systems and to improve the design of the websites. At the same time, these purposes are legitimate interests within the meaning of Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. 

The record consists of:

—  the page from which the file was requested

—  the name of the file

—  the date and time of the query

—  the amount of data transferred

—  the access status (transfer file, file not found)

—  the description of the type of web browser used

—  the description of the type of terminal used

—  the IP address of the requesting computer

2\. Customer Account

We offer our customers the opportunity to open a personal customer account. Hereby it is possible to view products that are to be purchased in limited edition and only for a short time on [MONOQI.co.uk](https://www.monoqi.co.uk/gb_en/). In addition, customers may use certain services (such as viewing order status and history, managing of credits and the newsletter). The legal basis for data processing is Article 6 (1) sentence 1 (a) or (b) of the General Data Protection Regulation. Before the first use, you can log in with Facebook or Amazon (see 4.3) or you register once again. For the new registration we need the following information from you: 

— E-mail address

— Password

When you shop in our online shop, we also collect the following information:

—  Title

—  First given name

—  Surname

—  Company (optional)

—  Country

—  Phone

—  Address (street name, house number, postal code, city, optional: additional address and region)

—  Optional: data of a packing station (postal number, packing station number, postal code and city, optional: region

—  Possibly data of a different billing address

—  Transaction data (goods, price, time of the transaction)

3\. Customer account with Facebook Connect / Amazon account

You can also sign up via your Facebook or Amazon account. The use of these login methods is subject to the data protection conditions and terms of use of the respective provider (Facebook or Amazon). By registering on [MONOQI.co.uk](https://www.monoqi.co.uk/gb_en/) via Facebook-Connect, your email address will be transferred from Facebook and the Facebook ID to [MONOQI.co.uk](https://www.monoqi.co.uk/gb_en/) so that you can register on our website and log-in in the future. When you log in via your amazon account, we will receive your e-mail address and postal code for the purpose of registration and log-in. The legal basis for this data processing is Article 6 (1) sentence 1 (b) of the General Data Protection Regulation. 

More information about Facebook Connect can be found [here](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php), you will find more information about logging in via your Amazon account [here](https://www.amazon.de/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy?ie=UTF8&nodeId=3312401). 

4\. Use of Google Analytics

To create our website as required, we create pseudonymous user profiles using Google Analytics based on Article 6 (1) sentence 1 (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. It is a product of Google Inc. ("Google"), Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, as we have activated IP anonymization on this website, your IP address will be truncated by Google beforehand within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states of the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the US and only then shortened. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide us with other services related to website activity and internet usage. These purposes are legitimate interests within the meaning of Article 6 (1) sentence 1 (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. 

You can contradict the creation of the pseudonymous user profiles at any time. There are several ways to do this: 

1\. One way to object to web analytics through Google Analytics is to set an opt-out cookie that instructs Google not to store or use your information for web analytics purposes. Please note that with this solution, the web analysis will only be made as long as the opt-out cookie is saved by the browser. If you want to set the opt-out cookie now, please click. 

2\. You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software. 

3\. Depending on the browser you are using, you have the option of installing a browser plug-in that prevents tracking. To do this, please click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) and install the browser plug-in that can be called up there. 

5\. Use of Google Optimize

We collect and store data for optimization purposes through the website analysis service Google Optimize. It’s a service of Google Inc. (Google) Hereby we test different variants of our website. This helps us to find out which variant suits best for our users. This helps us to improve and redesign our website. At the same time, these purposes are legitimate interests of Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is transmitted on a server in the USA and stored there. 

The data collection and storage can be contradicted at any time with effect for the future here. 

6\. Use of FullStory

This website also collects and stores user behavior data with FullStory, a full-service web analytics service provider of the FullStory Inc, 818 Marietta Street, Atlanta, GA 30318, USA. FullStory records user behavior on our website. Visitor recordings allow us to analyze them and then improve the visitors' website experience. These purposes are legitimate interests within the meaning of Article 6 (1) sentence 1 (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is transferred to and stored on a server in the United States. The tracking (that is, the collection of the data generated by the cookie and related to the use of the website) can be deactivated at any time. Please follow the instructions on [this](https://www.fullstory.com/optout). 

7\. Google Tag Manager

We use Google Tag Manager to track events on our websites, such as: clicking certain buttons. As a result, individual parts of the website are tagged, that is provided with a marker. We use this service to manage these website markers via a user interface. Cookies are not used and no personal data is collected. 

4\. How we use your data

4.1 Overview

Data that you submit to us as part of the registration process and when placing orders in the online shop is summarized for the following purposes: 

—  Establishment and provision of the customer account

—  Making your customer account available on our website

—  Processing of purchases in our online shop

—  Delivery of goods

—  Payment processing

—  Clarification of queries related to your customer account and / or abandoned orders

—  Information about changes to the terms and conditions or privacy policy

—  Needs-based design of the website and the online shop

—  Sending the newsletter

—  Sending information, if expressly requested

—  As otherwise described in this Privacy Policy

4.2 Processing of purchases in the online shop

We use your data for the processing of your purchases in our online shop, including any subsequent warranties. We only pass on your data to third parties as far as this is necessary for the performance of the contract, billing or delivery. When processing purchases in our online shop, we use service providers such as Transport or logistics companies, banks and other payment service providers. We provide them with the necessary data for the execution of the order. The service provider may use the data only to fulfill the task assigned to him. 

For the processing of orders in our online shop we need your name, your address data, on delivery to a packing station information about the packing station (postal number, packing station number, zip code and city, region). Your payment details are not stored with us, but sent directly to our payment service providers. We execute the order when our payment service provider confirms receipt of payment. We use your e-mail address to confirm the receipt of the order and to inform you about the status of the order. The legal basis for data processing is Article 6 (1) sentence 1 (b) of the General Data Protection Regulation. 

4.3 Newsletter

On our website you have the opportunity to subscribe to our free newsletter (MONOQI Daily, MONOQI Weekly and MONOQI Special). The newsletter informs about current offers of MONOQI. To register, we need your e-mail address. We use these to send you the newsletter. 

After submitting the registration form you will receive a confirmation e-mail from us. Registration will not take effect until you click on the link in the confirmation e-mail. You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time. Just use the newsletter settings in the customer login, the unsubscribe link at the end of each e-mail or send an e-mail to [hello@monoqi.co.uk](mailto:hello@monoqi.co.uk). 

Your e-mail address will then be deleted from the distribution system. The legal basis for data processing is your consent, which you can revoke at any time by e-mail to [hello@monoqi.co.uk](mailto:hello@monoqi.co.uk) as described above. 

4.4 Use-based online advertising

At this point, we would like to provide you with comprehensive information on the topic of usage-based online advertising. Our website or the website from which you have just been linked, anonymously collects and processes your usage behavior. As a result, you benefit as a user by receiving advertising that is more in line with your interests and by delivering less randomly distributed advertising. To record your usage behavior, a cookie is stored on your device. Cookies are small text files that are stored on the hard disk of your computer and allow the recognition, but do not allow personal identification of your person. In order to optimize advertising based on your interests, we work with different providers. At the same time, these purposes are legitimate interests of Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. 

Information is collected about your activities on this website (e.g., surfing behavior, visited subpages of the internet site). All usage data is stored using a pseudonym, so that a personal identification is basically excluded. In general, you can prevent the storage of cookies on your hard disk by selecting "Do not accept cookies" in your browser settings. You can also set your browser to ask you before you set cookies whether you agree. Finally, you can delete once set cookies at any time. How this works in detail, please refer to the help pages of your browser. If you do not accept cookies, this may result in functional restrictions of the website in individual cases. Please note that in the event of cookies being deleted, you may need to reactivate opt-out cookies that have been set. For the data collection for the delivery of usage-based online advertising, we use the following providers: 

Visit [www.youronlinechoices.com/de/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/de/) to learn more about usage-based online advertising and individual providers. There they also have the opportunity to object to the usage-based online advertising by single or all providers. 

We use Google's cross-device remarketing technologies to help you see targeted advertising on other websites based on your visit to our websites. 

How does remarketing work?

When you visit our websites, it is possible for Google to retrieve recognition features for your browser or device (e.g., creating a so-called browser fingerprint), evaluate your IP address or a recognition feature in the form of a small text file on your device stores (e.g., a so-called third-party cookie). It is also possible that Google links and stores your visit to our website with one or more of these recognition features in order to display our advertising on other sites on the Internet. 

The above-mentioned recognition features are configured as pseudonyms and can be used by Google to recognize your device on other websites. For example, if you visit a page that participates in Google's Display Network (ie displays ads on behalf of Google), Google may recognize your device and browser based on the above mentioned features. 

We can also provide our websites with so-called "remarketing tags". This means that we include keywords in our websites that contain statements about the content of the displayed page (such as product or service categories). The keywords we use have neither personal nor sensitive information. Google receives and stores these keywords to the above mentioned recognition features. So, when you visit a page that we tagged with a particular product category, Google stores that tag and assigns it to your recognition criteria. 

By doing this, we can use Google to advertise on other websites that are based on the visited pages . If you are visiting another website that participates in the Google Display Network, Google will be able to tell you, based on the recognition features and the keywords stored on these recognition features, whether and, if so, which of our advertisements you want to see. 

Optimizing advertising based on your interests is a legitimate interest of Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. 

For more information about how Google Remarketing technologies work, visit <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>. 

If you sign up for Google services with your own login credentials or use one or more of your own Google accounts, Google can combine the recognition features of different browsers and end devices. So, if Google has ever created its own recognition feature for the laptop, desktop, or smartphone or tablet you're using, these recognition features can be associated with each other once you've used or used a Google service with your login information. In this way, Google can target our advertising campaigns beyond end devices. However, Google will do so only if you have consented to this data processing in the past to Google. 

How can I object to advertising?

You can object to this form of advertising at any time. Please visit this page <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922> and disable personalized ads. Please note that these settings may not affect all devices and browsers. Further information is also available at <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922>. 

4.6 Google Conversion Tracking

To advertise our website, we also use the Google advertising tool "Google Adwords Conversion" from Google Inc. If you have reached our website via a Google ad, a cookie is stored on your computer. Cookies are small text files that your Internet browser stores and saves on your computer. These so-called "conversion cookies" lose their validity after 30 days and are not used for personal identification. If you visit certain pages on our website and the cookie has not expired yet, we and Google may recognize that you, as a user, have clicked on one of our Google-placed ads and have been redirected to our site. 

The information obtained through the "Conversion Cookies" is used by Google to create visitor statistics for our website. These statistics tell us the total number of users who clicked on our ad, and which pages on our site were subsequently accessed by their respective users. However, we or others through "Google Adwords" advertisers do not receive any information that personally identifies users. At the same time, these purposes constitute our legitimate interest within the meaning of Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. 

To learn how to prevent the installation of "Google conversion cookies", visit this page from Google: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/>. or more information about cookies and Google's privacy policy, please see the link below: [https://services.google.com/sitestats/en.html](https://services.google.com/sitestats/de.html). 

With your permission, we use the remarketing features of Facebook, Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook") on this site. The Facebook pixel is used to display users of our website when visiting the social network Facebook interest-based advertising. For this purpose, we have implemented the Facebook pixel on this website. This pixel is used to connect to the Facebook servers when visiting our website. It is transmitted to Facebook that you have visited our website. Facebook assigns this information to your Facebook account. The Facebook Pixel enables MONOQI to measure, evaluate and optimize the effectiveness of Facebook advertisements for statistical purposes and for market research purposes. MONOQI receives reports only in anonymous form from Facebook. For more information about the collection and use of data by Facebook, as well as your rights in this regard and ways to protect your privacy, please refer to the privacy policy of Facebook <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>. You may withdraw your consent to the use of the Facebook Pixel at any time with effect for the future by following this link <https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/>. For this you must be logged in to Facebook. 

In the context of usage-based online advertising, we also use the communication tool Custom Audience from Facebook. We generate a checksum (hash value) from your usage data (email addresses) and send it to Facebook for analysis and marketing purposes. Facebook compares the hash values ​​of our customer list with the hash values ​​of already existing own user data. Through the reconciliation, Facebook learns which of our customers is also a Facebook user. We learn if there is a match and can target our advertising efforts. The legal basis for the data processing is your consent, which you gave us when you first visited the website. You can revoke your consent at any time. For more information about the purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook and your options to protect your privacy, please refer to the privacy policy of Facebook, which you can see here: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>. You may withdraw your consent to the use of the Facebook Audience at any time with effect for the future by following this link <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>. For this you must be logged in to Facebook. 

4.8 Facebook Impressions

We use Facebook Impressions from Facebook, Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook"). We receive information about the frequency with which a product of our site is displayed. This way the frequency of the page views by the visitors of our website is recorded. At the same time, this purpose constitutes our legitimate interest of Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. Facebook uses cookies for Facebook impressions. The information generated by these cookies, such as time, location and frequency of your website visit, including your IP address, will be transferred to the Facebook servers in the United States. The storage of cookies can be prevented by appropriate settings in your browser. For more information about the collection and use of data by Facebook, as well as your rights in this regard and ways to protect your privacy, please refer to the privacy policy of Facebook <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>. 

4.9 Press distribution

For press representatives we offer the possibility to register for the press mailing list under ["Press"](http://press.monoqi.com/en). You will receive all press releases from MONOQI. To register, we need your e-mail address. We use these to send you the press releases. 

After submitting the registration form for the press mailing list, you will receive a confirmation e-mail from us. Registration will not take effect until you click on the link in the confirmation e-mail. You can unsubscribe from the press mailing list at any time. Simply use the unsubscribe link at the end of each e-mail. Your e-mail address will then be deleted from the distribution system. The legal basis for data processing is your consent, which you can revoke at any time as described above. 

4.10 Online-application

To apply online for an open position at MONOQI, an online application system is available on our website. The transmission of your data as well as the attached attachments are made via the website <https://monoqi.applytojob.com/apply/> via an encrypted connection. Your application data will be processed and transmitted to the USA via the online HR software JazzHR by Hireku, Inc. d / b / a Jazz, JazzHR. An adequate level of data protection is ensured by the Privacy Shield certification of Hireku, Inc. d / b / a Jazz. Your application data will be accepted by the HR department and forwarded to the department responsible for the advertised position or to the person entrusted with the processing. Legal basis for this data processing is § 26 Bundesdatenschutzgesetz. All involved treat your application documents with the necessary care and confidentially. After completion of the selection process, the information and the documents sent by you for the specific selection will be deleted after six months, unless we conclude an employment contract with you. 

Please note that applications you send us by e-mail will be sent to us unencrypted. We therefore recommend the use of the online application system. 

5\. Cookies

Cookies are small files that are stored on the hard disk of a visitor. They allow to keep information for a certain period of time and to identify the visitor's computer. Permanent cookies are used to control your visit to our website as well as to improve user guidance and individual performance. The legal basis for data processing is Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. You can set your browser to inform you about the placement of cookies. So the use of cookies becomes transparent for you. 

6\. Communication

You have the opportunity to contact us by e-mail at [hello@monoqi.co.uk](mailto:hello@monoqi.co.uk) or by phone. Your resulting data will only be processed to process your particular request. Disclosure to third parties will only be made to the extent necessary to process your request. The legal basis for the use of your data is Article 6 (1) (f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. MONOQI has a legitimate interest in being in contact with the users of the website and, if necessary, answering questions or sending information. 

7\. Partner Program

Under "Partner Program" you can register for the Partner Program of MONOQI. Registration is required if you wish to receive a certain fee for redirecting to our website or selling an item through this affiliate program, as a user has clicked on your link. The registration data will not be sent to us, but directly to the provider of this system, the affilinet GmbH, Sapporobogen 6-8, 80637 Munich. The legal basis for the use of your data is Article 6 (1) sentence 1 (b) of the General Data Protection Regulation. 

8\. Duration of data storage

We only store your data for as long as it is necessary for the provision of our services and the deletion does not conflict with any retention periods. 

9\. Use of service providers / processing of data in countries outside the European Economic Area

MONOQI uses service providers (order processing according to Article. 28 of the General Data Protection Regulation) to provide certain services and to process your data. The service providers process the data exclusively on the instructions of MONOQI and have been obliged to comply with the applicable data protection regulations. All processors have been carefully selected and will only have access to your data required for the provision of the services to the extent and for the period required. 

The servers of some service providers used by MONOQI are located in the US and other countries outside the European Union. Companies in these countries are subject to a data protection law that generally does not protect personal data to the same extent as is the case in the Member States of the European Union. To the extent that your data is processed in a country that does not have a recognized level of data protection such as the European Union, MONOQI uses contractual or other generally accepted instruments to ensure that your personal information is adequately protected. 

10\. Encryption

In order to protect your data against unwanted access, we use an encryption method on our website. Your information is then transferred from your computer to the server and vice versa via the Internet using a 256-bit TLS encryption (Transport Layer Security Version 1.2). You will recognize this by the lock icon on the status bar of your browser and the address bar beginning with https: // 

11\. Children

The website and the online shop of MONOQI are not aimed at persons under 18 years of age. Therefore, if you are under the age of 18, you may not use the MONOQI website and online store and may not enter your personal information on our website or online store. We do not knowingly collect data from persons under the age of 18. If you are a parent of a person under the age of 18 and you know that your child is using our website or our online store, please contact us using the contact details in Section 13 and arrange for the deletion of the relevant customer account. 

12\. Your rights as a user

As a user, you have the right to request information about what data is stored about you and for what purpose this storage takes place. In addition, you may correct incorrect data or delete data that is not permitted or no longer necessary to store. You have the right to data portability. You also have the right to complain to a regulatory agency about the processing of data. 

13\. Data Protection Officer

Our company data protection officer is at your disposal for information or suggestions concerning data protection:
